-亲爱的  -嘿
-Hey, hon. -Hey.
-你手里拿的啥  -宝宝监视器
-What you got there? -Our new baby monitor.
如果咱俩中的一人去楼上  我们现在就可以测下好不好使
Hey, you know, if one of us runs upstairs, We could test it out right now.
我说没怀孕的那个
The one of us who is not pregnant.
-我去吧  -嗯
-Hey, how about if I go?  -Mm-hmm.
准备就绪
Okay, all set!
好了  发出宝宝的声音吧
All righty, make baby noises.
好嘞  咕咕嘎嘎
All right. Goo goo ga ga.
啊哦  我尿布湿了
Uh-oh! My diapie is full!
谁能帮我换一下下呢
Will somebody "pwease" change me?
妈呀  我以为需要为这事担心还得再过几年呢
Aw, man. I didn't think we'd have to worry about this for years.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast</i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late</i> <i>and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>"Has anybody</i> <i>seen my left shoe?"</i>
■
翻译： Tracy
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes,</i> <i>take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride,</i> <i>laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is</i> <i>up on the roof</i>
■
校订： Johnny-Z
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there,</i> <i>I survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take</i> <i>my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know</i> <i>your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything</i> <i>turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life</i> <i>is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me,</i> <i>it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第五集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E05  Catch Me If You Can
-早啊孩子们  -早
-Morning, boys. -Morning.
今天我做早餐  老爸你想吃啥
I'm in charge of breakfast today, what would you like? Dad.
生猪肉20磅
20 pounds of raw pig.
你是想就着面包一起吃吗
You want toast with that?
不是  我要用它做诱饵
No, I need it for bait.
有条巨蟒溜进了斯隆湖
Believe it or not, we got a giant snake loose in Sloan's Lake.
看看  一条大水蟒
Look at that... an anaconda.
扯呢吧  水蟒怎么去得了丹佛市的呢
What? How could an anaconda get to Denver?
-谁知道呢  -没准是某个小孩
-Who knows? -Maybe some kid went to Florida
和祖父母一起去弗罗里达州度假后
On vacation with his grandparents,
带回来一条小蛇
Brought a baby snake back.
没准这小孩给它起名叫施耐普
Maybe the kid named him snappy.
没准施耐普后来长得太大  小孩被吓坏了
Maybe when snappy got too big, the kid freaked out.
然后就把它放走了
And set him free.
猜测而已
Just a guess.
不管怎样  这都是我一生难得的机遇啊
Anyway, this is the opportunity of a lifetime.
如果我能抓住这条蛇
I mean, if I can catch this snake,
我的声誉肯定会极大得提升啊
This is great publicity for the triple-b-g.
-啊  -啥
-Huh? -What?
鲍伯到  虫子跑
Bob's bugs be gone.
-噢  -对
-Oh oh! -Oh okay.
老爸  我能和你一起去吗
Hey, dad, can I come with you?
我想看看你是怎么被蛇抓住的
I'd love to see you get chased by a giant snake.
是蛇被我抓住
Hey! I'm gonna catch that giant snake.
管它谁被谁抓住  我都爱看
However it plays out, I just want to see something catch something.
-嗨  -嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
这么说我们也成了会穿情侣装的情侣了
So we've turned into that couple?
-我喜欢  -我也是
-I love it! -Me too.
-那么今晚  -嘘
-So about tonight... -No, shh!
说吧  安全了
Okay, coast is clear.
有必要弄的这么神秘吗
Do we really have to be so secretive?
你说笑呢吧
Are you kidding?
你知不知道要被我老妈发现了她得啥举动
Do you have any idea what would happen if my mom found out?
那我今晚来接你的时候  我们该怎么说呢
So when I pick you up tonight, what do we say we're doing?
甭担心  到时候编个就成  我演技很好的
Don't worry. I'll come up with something. I'm a pretty good actress.
首先  在这个家我演技最好
Okay, first of all, in this family, I am the greatest actress.
其次  没人能骗到老娘我
Second of all, nobody fools mama ames.
当然了
You bet.
查莉  等你到了你姐姐的年纪
Now, Charlie, when you're Teddy's age,
你不会编瞎话的对不对
You're not going to try to get away with stuff, are you?
-不  我会的  -哦
-Yes, I will. -Oh.
查莉  这个家谁演技最好
Charlie, who's the greatest actress in the family?
是你  妈妈
You are, mommy.
感觉好多了
All better.
P.J 我要和你谈谈
P.J., we need to talk.
我有个很危险的任务要交给你
I've got a dangerous mission for you.
米奇  我不会再尝那个巧克力奶昔了
Mitch, I am not trying the chocolate shake again.
我要你找出从店里偷鸡的人
I need you to find out who is stealing chicken from the store.
怎么会有人偷我们的鸡  难道他们都不尝下吗
Why would someone steal our chicken? Haven't they tasted it?
我也不知道  不过
I don't know, but...
老板肯定得为这事找我算账
Corporate is really busting my giblets about this.
所以我要派出我最得力的手下
So I am putting my best man on it.
-就是你呀  -噢
-You. -Oh!
那好啊  有啥线索没
Cool. Any idea who the thief is?
我确信是内贼干的  所以可能是贾斯汀
Okay, I'm pretty sure it's an inside job. So it could be Justin...
你的饭钱是三块  你给了我五块  所以
Okay, your meal was $3. And you gave me a $5, so...
别帮我  我能算出来
Don't help me. I got this.
还有可能是瓦尔  那个素食者
...Then there's Val, the vegetarian...
这是你的被谋杀的鸡
Here's your murdered chicken.
最后  大块头莱尼
...And finally, big Lenny.
你不吃了吧
You gonna finish that?
你有什么想法  你觉得谁是偷鸡的主谋
So what do you think, kid? Who's the master chicken thief?
凭直觉我认为是贾斯汀
Gut instinct? I gotta go with Justin.
五减三  还是三减五啊  好好想啊  贾斯汀
Three from five... Or was it five from three? Think, Justin. Think.
或者是瓦尔  可能是瓦尔
Or Val. Could be Val.
一旦蛇咬了肉  我就用这个套住它的脖子
So once the snake takes the meat, then I slip that over his neck.
一旦我抓到它  我就对着你的摄像机说
And then once I got him, I turn to your camera and I say,
安息吧  蛇儿
"take a break, snake!"
老爸  我可不想多想一旦你抓住蛇的场面
Ha. Dad, I wouldn't overthink the once-I've-got-him part.
我还需要句名言啥的
You know what? I still need a catchphrase,
汤姆·克鲁斯在电影里扮演我时会说的话
Something Tom cruise can say when he plays me in the movie.
晕  我是被分配错角色了吗  这句怎么样
How about, "boy, have I been miscast"?
盖比  不敢相信让你见到了
Uh, Gabe, I don't believe you've met
丹佛市最讨人厌的动物管制官
Denver's least-favorite animal-control officer.
你好啊  昆特
Hello, quint
你在这干吗呢  除虫小子
What are you doing here, bug boy?
是条蟒蛇逃掉了  又不是只白蚁
There's a monster snake on the loose, not a termite.
好吧  你不是在帮某位老太太从树上把小猫弄下来吗
Yeah. Shouldn't you be getting some old lady's Kitty out of a tree?
小松饼可以等会儿
Hmm? Muffin can wait.
首先  是我把那个冷血的畜生引进来的
First, I'm bringing in that cold-blooded beast out there.
你以前抓过类似的东西吗
Have you ever caught anything like this before?
这个应该能回答你的问题
Does this answer your question?
那是件T恤
That's a t-shirt.
我是来抓蛇的  不是来抓虫的
I'm here to catch a snake, not a cold.
看见伤疤没  我跟那个大白家伙扭打成一团
See that scar? I got that tangling with a great white.
-是鲨鱼吗  -拉布拉多犬
-Shark? -Labradoodle.
那些玩意可凶狠了
Those things are fierce.
面对现实吧  邓肯
Face it, Duncan, you're out of your league.
你是在自不量力  你只是个除虫的
You're an exterminator!
你打算怎么着  把湖面给罩上吗
What are you going to do, tent the Lake?
当然不是  我要用这个抓
Uh, no. I'm gonna catch him with this.
-我用这些抓  我的九个助手  -喔
-Well, I'm gonna catch him with these... My nine assistants. -Whoa.
-拉布拉多犬吃了我的小指  -噢
-Labradoodle got my pinkie. -Hmm.
你好  邓肯太太
Hi, Mrs. Duncan.
-你好  斯宾塞  进来吧  -谢谢
-Hi, Spencer. Come on in. -Thanks.
你们俩小家伙今晚打算干吗呢
So what you kids got planned for tonight?
呃  泰迪是怎么打算的呢
Um, what did Teddy say we were up to?
-她没打算  回答我的问题  -呃
-She didn't. Answer the question. -Uh...
-我来了  -泰迪
-Here I am! -Teddy.
你妈妈想知道我们今晚要干啥
Hi. Your mom wants to know what we're doing tonight.
我们要去看电影
We're going to the movies.
-什么电影  -二人桌
-Oh. Which one? -"table for two."
-是讲什么的  -供两个人坐的桌子
-What's it about? -A table for two.
-等级  -PG
-Rating? -Pg.
(普通级,宜在家长指导下观看)
-片长  -98分钟
-Running time? -98 minutes.
-你貌似备好了所有的答案  -你貌似备好了所有的问题
-You seem to have all the answers. -You seem to have all the questions.
我们走吧  斯宾塞
Let's go, Spencer.
-听上去你俩今晚活动很明确啊  -没错
-Sounds like you two have a very specific evening planned. -Yes, we do.
-祝你度过一个愉快的晚上  邓肯太太  -我会的
-Have a nice night, Mrs. Duncan. -I will.
就要变成三人桌了
"table for three."
噢
Oh!
别紧张  我不是入侵者
Do not be alarmed. I am not an intruder.
P.J.  你这是干吗
P.J., what are you doing?
我乔装打扮
I'm going undercover to figure out
以找出我的哪个同事是偷鸡贼
Which one of my co-workers is stealing chicken.
你以为他们见了甘道夫就会自首么
And you think they're going to open up when they see Gandalf?
（魔戒中的白胡子老头）
你有更好的主意
You got a better idea?
-嗯  戴个窃听器吧  -好主意
-Yeah, wear a wire. -Yes! I love it.
窃听器是啥东西
What's a wire?
一种录音装置  藏在衣服下面
A recording device. You wear it under your clothes.
然后就能录下来别人说的话
And then you can use what the people say against them.
-酷啊  我要戴个窃听器  -嗯
-Cool. I'll wear a wire.  -Yeah
我就像一个间谍  从中世纪来的间谍
I'll be like a spy. A spy from middle earth.
我就像你的弟弟  从地球来的
And I'll be like your brother. From planet earth.
才不是去看电影呢
Oh, movie my butt.
快乐时光要结束了
Party time's over.
你在表演  竟然不带我
You're doing a show... Without me!?
这就是你们要干的事  背着我排练音乐剧
So this is what you've been doing? Rehearsing a musical behind my back?
泰迪  你什么时候开始不爱我的
Teddy, when did you stop loving me?
老妈  我真不喜欢以这种方式被你发现
Mom, I was hoping you wouldn't find out this way.
事实上  我就希望不被你发现
Actually, I was just hoping you wouldn't find out.
你在表演“法兰妮拯救了农场”
And you're doing "franny saves the farm"?
那是我最爱的音乐剧啊
That's my favorite musical of all time.
还不止这些呢  她演的就是法兰妮
Not only that, she's playing franny.
别帮倒忙  富兰克林
Don't help me, Franklin.
那个  大家先休息五分钟吧
Hey, let's... let's take a five, everybody.
泰迪  你为啥不让我知道呢
Oh, Teddy, why would you keep this from me?
我可以帮你啊  教你  指导你
I could have helped you, taught you, mentored you.
你说的这三个构成了我没告诉你的理由
Yeah, and those are three of the reasons I didn't tell you.
你想说啥
What are you trying to say?
老妈  我每次想做点跟表演有关的事
Mom, anytime I try to do something.
你都要插上一手
That has to do with performing, you get involved.
不只是插手  就是接管了
And you don't just get involved; you take over.
那抱歉了  泰迪  好吧  我爱聚光灯
Well, I'm sorry, Teddy. Okay? I love the spotlight.
不过说实话  没有聚光灯爱我得多
But in fairness, not as much as the spotlight loves me.
老妈  我希望这次您别插手了  就这一次
Mom, I would like for you to not make this about you, just this one time.
求你了  只做我的老妈不行吗
Please, could you just be my mom?
那种带着花来  坐在观众席观看自己孩子表演的老妈
Moms bring flowers, they sit in the audience and they watch their kids.
-那我  -安静地看
-Well, I... -Quietly.
那好吧  我很抱歉我是一个不称职的妈妈
Well... I'm sorry I've been such a terrible mother.
别啊  老妈  我不是
No... no, mom, I didn't...
我就说聚光灯爱我吧
I told you the spotlight loved me.
Clark  别逞能
Clark, cut it out.
每小时14英里
14 miles per hour...
该睡觉了  盖比  明天还得抓蛇呢
Well, time to get some sleep, Gabe. Got a snake to catch tomorrow.
老爸  你有没有赤手空拳打倒过一头灰熊
Hey, dad, have you ever knocked out a grizzly bear with one punch?
让我想想  呃  没有
Well, let me think. Uh, no.
知道谁打倒过么  昆特
You know who has? Quint.
你怎么知道的
How do you know that?
我看了他的博客  名叫“视昆而止”
I'm reading this blog. It's called "quint while you're ahead."
-他真的好猛啊  -我和昆特一样猛啊
-Man, is he tough!  -Hey, I'm just as tough as quint.
不好说啊  老爸  也许你应该让他去抓蛇
I don't know, dad. Maybe you should leave the snake catching to him.
我是说  毕竟你是除虫专家啊  点燃除虫炸弹后就跑开了
I mean, you're an exterminator. You set off bug bombs and run.
我必须得跑啊  这是政府规定的呀
I have to run, Gabe. It's government mandated.
抓偷鸡贼的时间到了
Time to catch a chicken thief.
很高兴你们都能过来
So glad you all could come over,
贾斯汀  瓦尔  还有大块头莱尼
Justin, Val and big Lenny.
既然现在不是在工作
And we're away from work,
我们可以不拘礼节
So we can really let our hair down.
(字面意思:把头发放下来)
我一直把头发放下来的
I let my hair down at work all the time.
我还曾掉过一根在凉拌生菜丝里
I lost a scrunchie in the Cole slaw once.
伙计们  这是我们培养感情的好机会啊
Come on, guys, this is our chance to bond,
彼此分享一下希望与理想
Share our hopes, our dreams,
以及深藏心底的小秘密
Our darkest secrets.
谁先来  莱尼
Who wants to go first? Lenny?
我饿了
I'm hungry.
不错的开头  不是秘密  不过是个不错的开头
Good start. Not a secret, but good start.
要说秘密  为啥不从你开始呢
If we're telling secrets, why don't you go first?
好的  没问题啊
Okay. Okay.
我有时候从上班的地儿偷东西  有人要往下接吗
Uh, sometimes I steal supplies from work. Anybody want to piggyback on that?
-我曾经偷过一根吸管  -接着说
-I took a straw once. -Yeah yeah.
但是我感觉很不好  于是又放回去了
But I felt so bad, I brought back two.
-嗯  -什么声
-Ahem. Ah... -What was that?
-没啥  -听上去像是回音
-What was what? -Sounded like feedback.
我啥也没听见
I didn't hear anything.
老妈  你来这干吗
Mom, what are you doing here?
既然是儿童剧院  我想查莉应该会喜欢
Well, it is children's theater. I thought Charlie might like it.
她还给你带来了些东西
And she has something for you.
谢谢你  小查莉
Aw, Charlie, thank you.
好了  宝贝  我们走
Okay, come on, sweetie, let's go.
呃  老妈等一下
Oh, mom, wait. Um...
我昨天说的那些话很不好
About what I said yesterday, I was out of line.
然后捏
And?
我很抱歉
And I'm really sorry.
再然后捏
And?
没有了
That's all I got.
好吧  可能的确不全是你的不对
Okay. Well, you may not have been entirely wrong.
说到聚光灯  我可能也有些小问题
It might be possible that I have a small problem with the spotlight.
老妈  我们在后台  聚光灯打不到这的
Mom, we're backstage. The lights are out front.
所以我讨厌后台
That's what I hate about backstage.
不管怎么说  这是你闪耀光芒的时刻
Anyway, this is your moment to shine.
既然我们已经在这了
So as we say in the theater,
-那祝你好运  -噢
-Break a leg. -Oh.
(字面意思:跌断腿)
坏消息  富兰克林刚把腿摔断了
Terrible news... Franklin just broke his leg.
-他不能表演了  -那我们该怎么办
-He can't do the show. -Well, what are we going to do?
得再找个人演银行家琼斯  还得是熟悉这个角色的
I've got to find somebody to play banker Jones, somebody who knows the part.
我发誓跟我没关系
Okay, I swear I had nothing to do with this.
抓蛇的好日子啊
Yeah, good day to catch a snake.
你说对了  是好日子  一小时之前被我抓到送去动物园了
You're right! It was. I caught him an hour ago, took him to the zoo.
你抓到了
You did?
-那你还在这干吗  -干这个
-Well, then what are you doing here?  -Came back to do this. Nnnngg!
刚才那个是昆特吗
Aw, man, was that quint?
真好啊  多亏你让我去帮你拿薯片
Great. So I missed the coolest guy in the world.
让我错过了全世界最厉害的家伙
Because I had to get your potato chips.
重点是  你拿来了么
Hey, the point is, did you get 'em?
昆特看见蛇了吗
So did quint see the snake?
看见了  然后他
Yeah, matter of fact, he did. And then he...
然后他就走了  因为他害怕
And then he left... Because he was afraid.
昆特害怕了  -是的  不敢相信吧
Quint's afraid?  -Yeah. Can you believe that?
全世界最厉害的家伙因为害怕而离开了
Coolest guy in the world leaves because he's afraid.
不过你知道谁不害怕么  你家老头
But you know who isn't afraid? Your old man.
今儿个我要一次性把这事给了结了
And I am putting an end to this once and for all.
好了  给我出来吧  施耐普
All right. Come and get it, snappy!
爹啊  你确定你要这么做么
Dad, are you sure about this?
男人就应该  靠  水好冷啊
Hey, a man's got to do what a man's got... Oh man! This water is cold.
他在那干吗
What's he doing out there?
-抓蛇啊  -啥
-Catching the snake. -What?
-邓肯  我骗你的  -啥
-Duncan, I was lying! -What?
-我没抓着蛇  -是的  我在湖里
-I didn't catch the snake! -Yes, I am in the Lake!
-老爸  快回来  -我就是想摆脱你
-Dad, come back. -I was just trying to get rid of you.
-啥玩意  -喔  那是根木桩向他漂过去了吗
-What? -Whoa. Is that a log floating towards him or...
蛇啊
Sna-a-a-ake!
蛇在湖里啊
Snake in the Lake!
快上车  快上车  快上车  快上车
Get the truck, get the truck, get the truck, get the truck! Get the truck!
真是有其父必有其子
Like father, like son.
俩胆小鬼被根蠢木头吓得屁滚尿流
A couple of scaredy cats running from a stupid log.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
就这样么  你啥也没查出来
So that's it? You learned nothing?
我查到了大块头莱尼用叉子梳理胡子
I learned big Lenny combs his beard with a fork.
也就是说我们将永远都不会查出谁是偷鸡贼
So we'll never find out who's stealing the chicken.
老板会很失望的  这事将纠缠我一辈子了
Corporate is going to be devastated. This is going to haunt me forever.
-算了  -有件事比较有趣
-Oh well! -You know, funny thing though.
派对过后  我又回来看了下我们的保安监视录像
After the party, I came back here to look at our security-camera footage.
我们有保安监视录像
We, uh, have security cameras?
是啊  从录像上看有个人和你长得一样
Yeah. Yeah, and it showed this guy who looks just like you.
从冷藏室里拿走了几盒鸡
Taking boxes of chicken out of the storage fridge.
你有没有可能还有一个双胞胎兄弟
Do you by chance have an evil twin brother?
我不记得有啊
I don't recall.
然后你兄弟把偷的鸡放回车上
Then your brother put the stolen chicken in his car.
-这部分录像里也有啊  -是啊
-You got that on tape? -Uh-huh.
最扯的来了
And here's the crazy part...
你兄弟竟然和你开一样的车
Your brother drives the exact same car that you do.
这下不会错了  你真有个双胞胎兄弟
I guess that makes sense though. I mean, you are twins.
行了
All right!
别折磨我了  我坦白  是我偷的鸡
Quit toying with me. I confess. I stole the chicken.
我想自己开店
So I could open my own place,
米奇家禽折扣店
"mitch's discount poultry hut."
这么说你没有双胞胎兄弟
Wait. So you don't have a twin brother?
得了吧  算被你抓住了还不行么
Stop it, kid. You got me, all right?
我糊涂了 既然是你偷的鸡
Okay. Well, I'm confused. If you were the one stealing the chicken,
你为啥还让我去抓偷鸡贼呢
Why did you ask me to catch a chicken thief?
我不是你最得力的手下么
I mean, I'm your best man, right?
我没想到还能被你这个笨蛋抓住
I never thought someone so stupid could catch me.
这下看看谁才是笨蛋
Well, look who's stupid now.
我抓住了你还有你的双胞胎兄弟  是吧
'cause I just caught you and your twin brother. Right?
法兰妮  因为我没钱
franny, since I can't pay
他们就要收走我亲爱的农场
they're going to take my sweet farm away
不用担心  擦干眼泪
don't you worry, dry your eyes
我给你带来个大大的惊喜
'cause I just brought you a big surprise
-他是谁啊  -我是银行家
-who is this? -I'm the banker
-带着你的钱来了  -你该感谢她
-with your money -You should thank her
你是说我不用失去农场了
you mean I won't have to lose my farm after all?
只用打个电话而已
all it took was one little call
法兰妮拯救了农场
franny saved the farm
农场
farm!.
查莉  你当了一回小鸡
Well, Charlie, You were a little chicken.
很显然老爸也是
And apparently so was dad.
嘿  嘿  我可不是胆小鬼
Hey hey! I was not chicken.
我让那湖瞬间得到超多的关注
I was exiting the Lake in a rapid fashion.
没事的老爸  我宁愿要一个活着的懦夫也不要一个挂了的英雄
No, dad, it's all right. I'd rather have a live coward than a dead hero.
谢谢你了  儿子
Oh, thank you, son.
活着的英雄当然是最好的  不过
Yeah. Live hero would have been the best, but...
当然  如果真要排名的话
Of course. I mean, if you're going to rank them,
第一是活着的英雄  其次活着的懦夫
You'd want your live hero, live coward.
然后是挂了的英雄  挂了的懦夫
Yeah. You know, dead hero, dead coward.
懦夫还搞挂了  也太锉了
Yeah, dead coward. Those guys are losers.
你俩能消停会不  我正在弄视频日记呢
Hey, do you guys mind? I'm trying to do a video diary here.
说  祝你好运  查莉  不就完事了吗
Just say "good luck, charlie" and be done.
不像你说得那么简单好吧  应该
Look, it's not that easy. It's...
祝你好运喽  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
-呃  -在下面呢
-Huh.  -Down here.
哦  是你啊  施耐普
Oh, hey, it's you. Hello, snappy.
P.J  好久不见啊  朋友
P.J. Long time, amigo.
-你看上去不错啊  -省省吧
-Uh, you... you look well.  -Save it!
你怎么可以这样对我
How could you do this to me?
施耐普  我去拿冰激凌了  你可以跳进湖里啊
"snappy, why don't you hop in the Lake While I get us some ice cream"?
我是去拿冰激凌了呀
Well, I got ice cream.
但是你再也没回来了
But you never came back.
你再也没  噢  美味呀  这是啥东西
You never came... oh! Oh, yummy yummy. What is this?
这是查莉  你想都别想
This is Charlie and don't even think about it!
尝一口都不成吗
Not even a nipple.
谢谢你的来访  施耐普
Thanks for stopping by, snappy.
谁啊
Who is it?
-给查莉送玩具的  -走开
-Toy delivery for Charlie.  -Go away!